Nirmala Devi A/P Perumal No.5, Selasar Loke Lim, Taman Loke Lim, 30010 Ipoh, Perak

October 12, 2015

#### YEE LEE EDIBLE OILS SDN BHD

Lot 85, Jalan Portland, Tasek Industrial Estate, Ipoh, 31400, Ipoh, Perak

Dear Sir /Madam,

I am writing to apply for the HR & Admin Executive position via online. I am a well-qualified in Diploma in Management with Multimedia who would be an excellent choice for this position.

I have an ability to grow with a job, handle responsibility and build positive relationships with work colleagues at all levels. My present employer is very satisfied with my work rate, and I am confident that I can bring the same level of high performance to your company.

I very much hope that you will look favorably upon my application by recognizing my enthusiasm, talents in the field of HR & Admin Executive and my future potential. Please see my resume for additional information on my experience. Thank you in advance for your time and consideration.

Sincerely,

Nirmala Devi A/P Perumal



#### NIRMALA DEVI A/P PERUMAL

Address: No.5, Selasar Loke Lim, Taman Loke Lim, 30010 Ipoh, Perak.

Contact No.: 013-2759283/05-2916355 E-mail: n.devi2106@yahoo.com

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Age

: 27 years

IC No.

: 880531-08-5110

Date of Birth

: 31st May 1988

Sex

: Female

Nationality Race

: Malaysian

Religion

: Indian

: Hindu

**Marital Status** 

: Single

Health

: Excellent

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Hardworking and like new challenges, self-motivated, show initiative, positive working attitude, able to accept criticism, good communication skill, caring and able to work effectively in a team.

### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

#### **Tertiary Level:**

2008 – 2010 Multimedia College, Kuala Lumpur Diploma in Management with Multimedia CGPA: 2.70

#### **Secondary Level:**

2001 – 2006 Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Tasek Damai

SPM Grade: 1A 2B 3C 3D

PMR Grade: 1A 5C 2D

**Primary Level:** 

1995 – 2000 Sekolah Jenis Kebangsaan (Tamil) Sungai Pari

UPSR Grade: 4B 2C 1D

WORKING EXPERIENCE		
No.	Place	Work Description/ Position Title
1.	Hovid Bhd	Operator (8 month)
	(2008)	
2.	TM Point (Practical)	Sales and Purchase (4 month)
	(2010)	
3.	ISTA (Ipoh Skill Training Academy)	Admin (4 month)
	(2011)	
4.	J S OLIKH & CO (Lawyer Office)	Clerk (1 year)
	(2011-2012)	
5	Hovid Bhd	QA Clerk
	(July 2012- Present)	

# STRENGHT AND QUALITIES

- Strong analytical ability, good communication skills with people from all levels.
- Motivated efficient, accurate and detail oriented.
- High- energy, enthusiastic and dependable individual who excels in challenging and competitive environment.

	ADDITIONAL SKILLS
Languages	Able to communicate and write in Malay, English and Tamil.
IT Skills	<ul> <li>Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point, Microsoft Outlook, Microsoft Publisher, Macromedia Flash and Internet Accessibility.</li> </ul>
<b>Attended Trainings</b>	Good Manufacturing Practices & Hygiene Practice
(Hovid Bhd)	QA & QC Function
	Good Storage Practice
,	Line Clearance
,	<ul> <li>Documentation and Records</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Mix-ups and ways of reducing mix ups in Pharmaceuticals</li> </ul>
	Microbiological Aspect of Manufacturing
	Contamination in Manufacturing
6.1	Facility in Pharmaceutical
	Safety on hand, finger and hearing protection

### SALARY

**Current Salary** 

: RM 1100

Expected Salary

: RM 1500 (negotiable)

# REFEREES

1) Name

: Ms. Shamini

Tel No.

: 03-20204504

Position

: Lecture in MMC and Advisor

Company

: Multimedia College

Address

: Multimedia College, Jalan Gurney, Kuala Lumpur

2) Name

: Ms. Norafieza

Tel No.

: 05-2014623

Position

: HR Executive

Company

: Hovid Bhd

Address

: Hovid Bhd, Chemor

3) Name

: Ms. Sarinah

Tel No.

: 05-2014623

**Position** 

: QA Executive

Company

: Hovid Bhd

Address

: Hovid Bhd, Chemor